Dr. David Ashley White Papers, 1965-2001
University of Houston Libraries
- Scores and Manuscripts, 1965-2001 (Box 1-20)
  - Hymn Tunes, 1970-2000 (Box 18-20)
    - Darr, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Delta, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Denson, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Elizabeth Rose, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Eucharist, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Exalted Name, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Expectation, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Fesperman, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Fesperman New, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Festive Day, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Fifth Day, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - The First Song of Isaiah, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Gloria, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Grinnell, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Hammerling, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Heal Me, Hands of Jesus, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Herbert, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Holy Trinity, The American Cathedral, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Homage, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Hope of Peace, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Janet, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - John's Christmas Carol, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Jonathan, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Josephine, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Joyful Day, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Julian, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Justin, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Keiser, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Kennan, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Kennan New, undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Kingdom of Love, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Kirckman, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - A Labor Hymn, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Living String, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Lowry New, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Lynn, undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Majesty, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Margaret, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Marsh, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Maryville College, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - McGehee, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Memorial, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Messner, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Morning Star, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Mt. Calm, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Mystical Body, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Nashua, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Old Plum Grove, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Owens, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Palmer Church, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Plate, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Plum Groves, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - The Praising Word, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Proffitt, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Psalm 30, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Reunion, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Rhoads, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - River Potomac, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Robert, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Robert Arthur, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Rochester, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Rubric for Good Friday, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Rushing Wind, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - St. Andrew by the Sea, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - St. Bartholomew the Great, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - St. Francis, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - St. John's Kingston, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - St. Mark's Chapel, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - St. Paul's, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - St. Paul's Choir, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Sheridan, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Simms, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Simpson, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Skillman, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Song of the Redeemed, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Song to the Lamb, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Southwark Cathedral, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Sumter, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Sumter, revised, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Taylor, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - The Third Song of Isaiah, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Timbergrove, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Tucker, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Walker, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Ward, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Wedding Prayer, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Wildridge, August 26, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Winston, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Wordsworth, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Zechariah IV, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Zechariah's Song, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Three Hymn Settings - Not Published, May 12, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Proofs for David Ashley White Hymnary, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Hymns and Verses, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - A Philosophy for Hymnal Revision, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 19-20)
    There are three folders in this sub-series containing unidentified scores, musical notebooks, and manuscript fragments. These scores, while unidentified, most certainly relate to the compositions found in the preceding folders.
    - Unidentified scores, undated (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Three Music Writing Books, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Manuscripts, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript Fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Programs, 1964-2000 (Box 20-24)
  There are five boxes in this series consisting of various programs of performances of David Ashley White's works. Dr. White's works have been performed extensively throughout North America and Europe. The programs are arranged chronologically. Venues with large numbers of performances have been foldered separately, placed in chronological order, and are found at the end of the series.
  - Programs, 1964-1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Programs, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Programs, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Programs, January-June 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Programs, July-December 1999 (Box 23a, Folder 1)
  - Programs, January-June 2000 (Box 23a, Folder 2)
  - Programs, July-December 2000 (Box 23a, Folder 3)
  - Programs, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - St. Paul's United Methodist Church, Houston, 1989-1993 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - St. Paul's United Methodist Church, Houston, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - St. Paul's Westminster Abbey Trip, July 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - St. Paul's Westminster Abbey Trip Photos, July 1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - St. Paul's - Rochester, Michigan, 1989-2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Palmer Memorial Episcopal Church, Houston, 1989-2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Christ Church Cathedral, Houston, 1989-2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - The Houston Chamber Choir, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - American Guild of Organists (AGO) - Misc., 1985-2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Oversize Program Notices and Flyers, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1969-2000 (Box 25-29)
  This series consists of five boxes and has been divided into five sub-series: Publishers, Selah Publishing, Individuals, Miscellaneous Letters, and Kent Kennan. The box of Selah Publishing materials (box 25, folder 22) contains relevant catalogs of Dr. White's music.
  - Publishers, 1978-2000 (Box 25, Folder 1-19)
    There are nineteen folders in this sub-series arranged alphabetically by publisher, then chronologically within each folder.
    - Alfred Publishing, 1990-1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Augsburg Fortress Publishing, 1983-1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Canterbury Press, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Choristers Guild, 1988-1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Church Hymnal Corporation, 1978-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Concordia Publishing House, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Hindshaw Music Inc., 1988-1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Hope Publishing Co., 1989-1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Kevin Mayhew, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Lawson - Gould, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - MMB Music Co., 1990 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Morning Star, 1988-1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Oregon Catholic Press, 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Paraclete Press, 1985-2000 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Randall M. Egan, 1989-1997 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - St. James Music Press, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Swawnee Press, 1988-1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Theodore Presser Co., 1985-1991 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Publishers A - Z, 1989-2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Selah Publishing, 1984-2000 (Box 25-26)
    There are nine folders in this sub-series containing correspondence, catalogs, various hymns and hymn proofs.
    - Letters, 1984-1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Letters, 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Catalogs, 1993-1999 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Various Hymns of David Ashley White, Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - New Songs of Rejoicing Hymnal, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - First set of Proofs for David Ashley White Hymnary, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Second set of Proofs for David Ashley White Hymnary, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Various Hymn Proofs, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Various Proofs, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Individuals, 1978-2000 (Box 26-27)
    There are twelve folders in this sub-series arranged alphabetically by last name. Correspondents include David Tomatz, former Director of the School of Music; James Pickering, former President of UH; and Christoper Theofanidas, one of Dr. White's many students.
    - John Bennett, 1984-1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Emily Croom, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Carl Daw, Jr., 1985-1996 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Joseph Horovitz, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Richard Leach, 1993-2000 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Philip H. Mayor, 1978-1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Elena Nikolaidi, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - James H. Pickering, 1982-1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - James Pipkin, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Christopher Theofanidas, 1988-1998, (See Audio Cassettes box 37, items 6-11) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - David Tomatz, 1986-1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Margaret R. Tucker, 1983-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1969-2000 (Box 27-28)
    There are nine folders in this sub-series consisting of cards and letters from various churches, universities, and individuals. Items are arranged chronologically except for non-dated material found in box 28, folder 3.
    - Letters - Churches, 1984-2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Letters - Universities, 1980-1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Letters - Miscellaneous, 1980-2000 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - CD at St. Paul's, Houston, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Plymouth Music Series of Minnesota, 1993-1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Kent Kennan, 1984-1998 (Box 28-29)
    There are two boxes containing sixteen folders in this sub-series. The folders are arranged chronologically and include manuscripts and published scores as well as books by Kent Kennan used by David Ashley White.
    - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Letters: White to Kennan, 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Letters to Kennan, 1986-1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Book: The Technique of Orchestration 2nd ed., 1970 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Book: The Technique of Orchestration 4th ed., 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Music Score: Retrospectives, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript of Scherzo, Aria, and Fugato, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Published Score of Scherzo, Aria, and Fugato, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Photocopied Score of Threnody, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Music Score: Ca..., Diagramme pour Orchestre copyright 1974, by Eugene Kurtz, Inscribed to Kent Kennan, September 15, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Professional Activities, 1963-2000 (Box 30-33)
  There are over three boxes in this series which has been divided into four sub-series: University of Houston Moores School of Music, Legal, Conferences and Papers, and Clippings and Articles.
  - University of Houston Moores School of Music, 1981-2000 (Box 30-31)
    There are eighteen folders in this sub-series covering Dr. White's work at the University of Houston and The Moores School of Music. Materials include correspondence, awards, promotion and tenure materials, articles, student programs, and class schedules.
    - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
      - Moores School of Music, 1983-2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Congratulatory Notes on Directorship of Moores School of Music, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Cards and Letters from David Ashley White Students, 1990s (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - KUHF, 1988-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Awards, Promotion and Tenure (Box 30, Folder 5-12)
      - Curricula Vitae, 1990-1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Faculty Report (tenure), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Supplemental Materials (tenure), 1998 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Personal Music Catalogs, 1984-1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Evaluations and Honors, 1982-1999 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - HFAC Teaching Award, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Mayoral Resolutions and oversize awards, 1989,1991,1993 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Faculty Development Leave Committee, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - UH Limited Grant-in-aid Program, 1985,1988 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Interview and Articles (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
      - Interview Cassette and Transcript, November 23, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - UH - News about David Ashley White, 1981-2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Moores School of Music - Upscale Weekly, 1993-1998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Students (Box 31, Folder 4-6)
      - Student Programs, 1986-1996 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Student Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Class Schedules, 1991-1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Legal, 1972-2000 (Box 31, Folder 7-12)
    There are six folders in this sub-series dealing primarily with the legal aspects of music publishing. Included are materials related to Dr. White's membership in the American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), contracts, and copyright permissions. This sub-series is arranged chronologically.
    - ASCAP - Award Applications, 1990-1999 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - ASCAP - Award Notifications, 1985-2000 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - ASCAP - Award UH Congratulations, 1992-1999 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Contracts, 1978-1998 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Permissions, 1972-1999 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Donation to UH Special Collections, 1993-1996 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Conferences and Papers, 1963-2000 (Box 31-32)
    There are fifteen folders in this sub-series containing a variety of papers Dr. White has presented during his professional career. It is arranged alphabetically by organization name, title of the paper, or geographic location, as appropriate.
    - AGO Presentation at Temple Emanuel, November 6, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - American Anglican Tradition vs British, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - American Festival for the Arts, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Association of Anglican Musicians, 1984-2000 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Diocese of Texas Convention music (oversize), February 7, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Diocese of Texas Convention music (oversize), February 7, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - England Conference, June 21-30, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Evergreen Conference, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Handel and His Place in English Music, March 18, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - The Hymn Society, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Master of Operetta article, March 1974 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Mississippi Conference, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Mississippi Conference, 1995,1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Mississippi Conference Talk on Setting a Text, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Pre-concert talk - Harpsichord Society, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Programs Notes by David Ashley White, 1979-1996 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Texas Choral Directors Association, July 26-29, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Worship Journeys, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Clippings and Articles, 1976-2000 (Box 32-33)
    There are eight folders in this sub-series containing reviews of performances and compositions taken from local and national newspapers and professional journals.
    - Chorister Guild Letters, November 1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Houston Chronicle, 1976-2000 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Houston Post, 1981-1992 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - The Hymn: A Journal of Congregational Song, July 1991-April 1999 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - The Journal of the Association of Anglican Musicians, 1994-2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Pan Pipe Articles, 1979-1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Worship Arts, September/October 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Reviews, 1970s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Personal Materials, 1947-1998 (Box 33, Folder 5-16)
  There are thirteen folders in this series containing various personal items including photographs, materials from Dr. White's education, poetry, and musical scores composed by other individuals.
  - Photographs, Miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Del Mar College Diploma (A.A.), 1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - UH Undergraduate Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Classroom Handouts, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Poetry of J. Pittman McGehee, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Thunder Games and Lightning and other poems C.E. Cooper, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Be Thou My Vision for Oboe, Obligato, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Concerto for Oboe and Strings Corelli-Barbirolli, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Fantasy On A Moravian Hymn Robert Starer, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Three Songs: Upon A Bridge; I Remember, I Remember; and O That `Twere Possible music by Randy Harper, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Variations on an Original Chorale by Paavo Jam, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Vocalise Trio by Sergei Rachmaninoff arranged by Harold Suggs, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Audio/Visual Materials, 1973-2000 (Box 34-39)
  There are seventy-eight items in this series including audio cassettes, record albums, and a video. Contents of these items include various performances of Dr. White's compositions and lectures by or interviews with Dr. White. Some items are arranged alphabetically and some by topic.
  - Audio Cassettes (Box 34-38)
    - Amarillo Canticles, undated (Box 34, Cassette 1)
    - And Then The Bread, undated (Box 34, Cassette 2)
    - Elegy and Exaltation, undated (Box 34, Cassette 3)
    - Eliz Images, undated (Box 34, Cassette 4)
    - Hymns, undated (Box 34, Cassette 5)
    - Into the Woods, undated (Box 34, Cassette 6)
    - I will Arise, undated (Box 34, Cassette 7)
    - Lord My Shepherd, undated (Box 34, Cassette 8)
    - O God of Love: DAW White, undated (Box 34, Cassette 9)
    - O Light of Light, August 30, 1992 (Box 34, Cassette 10)
    - O Light: St. Paul's, February 21, 1993 (Box 34, Cassette 11)
    - The Lord My Shepherd, undated (Box 34, Cassette 12)
    - Pelican, undated (Box 34, Cassette 13)
    - Ring the Broken Pail, undated (Box 34, Cassette 14)
    - Songs of the Queen's Road, March 14, 1997 (Box 34, Cassette 15)
    - Star In The East, undated (Box 34, Cassette 16)
    - This Glimpse of Glory, undated (Box 34, Cassette 17)
    - White: When In Our Music (Palmer), undated (Box 34, Cassette 18)
    - White - Triptych, 1979 (Box 35, Cassette 1)
    - White: Excerpts (Master Tape), undated (Box 35, Cassette 2)
    - Choral Music Sampler, 1988 (Box 35, Cassette 3)
    - Excerpts (February 1990.), February 1990 (Box 35, Cassette 4)
    - A Collage of Song- Harriet McCleary, Soprano, February 14, 1995 (Box 35, Cassette 5)
    - Recital Tape A, 1973 (Box 35, Cassette 6)
    - White: Organ Music, undated (Box 35, Cassette 7)
    - Palmer Church: Organ, July 10, 1987 (Box 35, Cassette 8)
    - Night Cries - Organ, undated (Box 35, Cassette 9)
    - Pipe Dreams - AGO Highlights, 1988 (Box 35, Cassette 10)
    - Phantasy and Toccata - Timothy Hester, piano, 1997 (Box 35, Cassette 11)
    - KUHF Interview, February 17, 1992 (Box 35, Cassette 12)
    - Radio Interview, 1995 (Box 35, Cassette 13)
    - David Ashley White KUHF, February 27, 1996 (Box 35, Cassette 14)
    - Dr. David Ashley White Recording, October 25, 1999 (Box 35, Cassette 15)
    - CD Tape A and B, May 1996 (Box 35, Cassette 16)
    - CD Take #1 - 53, January 27-28, 1995 (Box 35, Cassette 17)
    - CD Take #1 - 22, January 28, 1995 (Box 35, Cassette 18)
    - Ass't Songs, June 9, 1980 (Box 36, Cassette 1)
    - St. Paul's UMC O Lord, Forgive, January 7, 1980 (Box 36, Cassette 2)
    - St. Paul's Choir - Evensong, July 16, 1989 (Box 36, Cassette 3)
    - Evensong in Westminster Abbey, 1989 (Box 36, Cassette 4)
    - Evensong, June 30, 1991 (Box 36, Cassette 5)
    - Palm Sunday, 1991 (Box 36, Cassette 6)
    - Palm Sunday, 1993 (Box 36, Cassette 7)
    - Easter - 1st Service, 1994 (Box 36, Cassette 8)
    - Palmer Memorial Church, undated (Box 36, Cassette 9)
    - Civic Chorus, Spring, 1980 (Box 36, Cassette 10)
    - University of Alaska, March 3, 1991 (Box 36, Cassette 11)
    - American Choral Directors Assoc., March 13-16 1991 (Box 36, Cassette 12)
    - ACDA National Convention, 1993 (Box 36, Cassette 13)
    - Closing Service- AAM, June 27, 1986 (Box 36, Cassette 14)
    - David White - HMC, undated (Box 36, Cassette 15)
    - White Evensong - A+B, undated (Box 36, Cassette 16)
    - DMC Closing Service, 1985 (Box 36, Cassette 17)
    - Hymn Presentation - Oberlin, OH, July 1996 (Box 36, Cassette 18)
    - Interfaith AIDS Memorial Service, November 8, 1992 (Box 37, Cassette 1)
    - Christ Church Cathedral Choir - San Antonio, 1996 (Box 37, Cassette 2)
    - John's Christmas Carol - Master, January 5, 1992 (Box 37, Cassette 3)
    - In Memory of Betty Deming, undated (Box 37, Cassette 4)
    - Kennan - Threnody, October 2, 1992 (Box 37, Cassette 5)
    - Music of Chris Theofanidas, undated (Box 37, Cassette 6)
    - Theofanidas, undated (Box 37, Cassette 7)
    - Chris Theofanidas, undated (Box 37, Cassette 8)
    - Etenraku - Chris Theofanidas, 1996 (Box 37, Cassette 9)
    - Recent Music of Chris Theofanidas, undated (Box 37, Cassette 10)
    - I Saw A New Heaven - Chris Theofanidas, 1995 (Box 37, Cassette 11)
    - P.H. Mayor - Synthesizers, undated (Box 37, Cassette 12)
    - Ndizi Tatu - Eric McIntyre, undated (Box 37, Cassette 13)
    - Three Eliz. Images (Randy), undated (Box 37, Cassette 14)
    - Chris Popelka (student), undated (Box 37, Cassette 15)
    - John Bennett - The Struck Leviathan, 1977 (Box 37, Cassette 16)
    - Christmas Day and Introit by John Bennett, undated (Box 37, Cassette 17)
    - Beyond the Compass Rose by John Bennett, September 30, 1983 (Box 37, Cassette 18)
    - Singing New Songs of Rejoicing, 1994 (Box 38, Cassette 1)
    - Cimoarosa Quartet, undated (Box 38, Cassette 2)
    - David White - HMC, undated (Box 38, Cassette 3)